Wow, ha, so you guys are, like, buds now?
(Raj:)Oh, yeah. We hang out all the time.
(Stuart:)He doesn't have a girlfriend,
I don't have a girlfriend.
(Raj:)It's like we both had these holes in our lives,
but now we fill each other's holes.
(Stuart:)That sounds a little funny
to an American ear.
- Which part?
- Just all of it.
Okay, so, what...?
What do you guys got going on, tonight?
(Stuart:)Raj is taking me
to the Sound of Music sing-along.
(Howard:)Sound of Music sing-along?
That used to be our thing, but that's cool.
(Raj:)Howard, it's still our thing. Come with us.
We'll get you a scalped ticket.
(Howard:)So I'd be sitting by myself?
(Raj:)We'll switch.
You'll come sit with me after intermission.
(Howard:)So I'd be sitting by myself
during "Edelweiss"?
(Howard:)No, no, you guys go.
(Howard:)Have fun.
- Okay. Will I get to see you tomorrow?
- Absolutely. See you, Stuart.